Siddharth Senapati

Puri, Odisha 752107 | (+91) 8093268659 | <u>siddharthsenapati09318@gmail.com</u> | github.com/SiddharthSenapati | https://www.linkedin.com/in/siddharth-senapati-b35896256/

Profile

Hard-working and enthusiastic Junior Software Developer with years of practical experience in web application designing, development and deployment with ASP .NET Web Applications and MVC. Collaborate effectively within a team, troubleshoot issues, and deliver high-quality solutions within tight timelines. Looking forward to applying my abilities.

Experience

.NET DEVELOPER | KYTE TECHNOLGY, BHUBANESWAR | JUNE 2023 - DECEMBER 2023

• Joined as a Trainee and upgraded to Full-Time Junior Developer within 3 months period. Assisted actively in web Development projects, debugged, added new features and acquired hands-on experience in technologies such as ASP .NET, SQL and JavaScript.

.NET DEVELOPER | CONCEPT INFOWAY PVT. LTD. AHMEDABAD | JAN 2024 - PRESENT

- Flourishing at Concept Infoway, where I bring web applications to with ASP.NET, MVC, C#, and SQL Server. A master of efficiently solving approximately 15 Jira issues per week and bringing the coding optimization approximately 14%, so our clients remain ahead at all times.
- An energetic team player who works across functions to create, test and release quality web solutions, delivering on-time excellence, every time.

Education

MASTERS IN COMPUTER APPLICATION | BPUT, ODISHA | 2022-24 (CGPA – 8.45) BSC IN PHYSICS | UTKAL UNIVERSITY, ODISHA | 2019-22 (CGPA – 8.88)

Skills & Abilities

- · ASP .NET Web Forms
- · ASP .NET MVC
- · C#
- · JQUERY

- · ASP .NET Core Web API
- · SQL Server
- · 00PS
- Java

Projects

EMPLOYEE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

Created a strong and effective Task Management System with.NET MVC which is meant to streamline and improve task allocation, tracking, and management within teams. The application takes advantage of the Model-View-Controller design to provide a clean separation of worries, enhancing maintainability and scalability.

FULL FLEDGED REGISTRATION PAGE

Developed and coded a complete registration page with.NET in a 3-tier architecture, JQuery to achieve a solid, maintainable, and scalable process of user registration. The application takes advantage of the clean segregation of presentation, business logic, and data access layer for reusability.